<news>

<newsitem headline="License Key Price Drop">
<text>Basic and premiuim key license have had a price drop. Basic keys are now 1.00 and Premium keys are now 3.25</text>
<date>11 July 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Developer Preview Builds">
<text>DP Builds will be available soon on xda labs as the Alpha builds. I will announce on the google plus group when they will be live. These builds will be available to anyone who wants to help locate bugs or just get a taste of what 11.3 will have instore for them and dont mind the spoilers. All feedback will be submitted to the xda forums or google plus group. See you on the forums! </text>
<date>6 July 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Papers Maintenance Issues">
<text>Their are reports of the Sapphire wallpaper archives not loading correctly or crashing on loading all wallpapers. This issue is being tracked.</text>
<date>26 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Update 11.3 schedule update">
<text>Notice! 11.3 official update will be released after a temporary soak testing with the xda and google plus communities. An alpha build or dev preview will be available to try on xda labs soon. Regards</text>
<date>26 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Game with the dev">
<text>HMU up on the Sony Playstation 4! PSN Dracos_Aura Favorite games are Battlefield and Destiny!</text>
<date>20 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="GocalSD Website Improvements">
<text>GSD has gone through some visual maintenance. Go ahead and check it out. More visual additions will be added soon as well as an exclusive section for Sapphire Launcher.</text>
<date>20 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Ratings and Reviews">
<text>Don't forget to update your reviews on google play and xda labs! If you haven't had the moment to rate Sapphire UI, take the time todo so. Ratings are part of the community focus and user feedback program and updates usually are forged and based on feedback. Let us build something together.</text>
<date>12 May 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Backers">
<text>Grab an Onyx License to show off true backing support. Adds Onyx Subscriber to Sapphire launcher settings subtitle.</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Google Plus">
<text>Join the Google Plus Group to get in on exclusive sneak peaks, dev previews, and one on one dev support!</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Papers">
<text>Wallpapers will be updated on a monthly basis based on top picks of the android communities.</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome and Thankyou for your support!">
<text>Enjoy your stay, Ask questions, get involved with the communities and stay active! Sapphire UI is the community custom launcher powered by google exclusively for Android 5.0+</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

</news>
