<news>
  
  <newsitem headline="Papers Maintenance">
<text>Sapphire Launchers Wallpaper archives will be acting wonky for the next 3 hrs as I make changes to the archives and add new optimal wallpapers to your selection. Report back any bad behavior on google plus.</text>
<date>23 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Update 11.3 schedule">
<text>Scheduled for a release near the end of june. 11.3 will feature a large amount of fixes, improvements, material improvements, and a few new tweaks for users to try out. Watch the Google Plus Group feed for previews and suggest feedback before the release.</text>
<date>20 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Game with the dev">
<text>HMU up on the Sony Playstation 4! PSN Dracos_Aura Favorite games are Battlefield and Destiny!</text>
<date>20 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="GocalSD Website Improvements">
<text>GSD has gone through some visual maintenance. Go ahead and check it out. More visual additions will be added soon as well as an exclusive section for Sapphire Launcher.</text>
<date>20 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="A Special Thanks">
<text>You've raised over 300 dollars in donations for the month of may in Sapphire UI keys. That is outstanding! Lets make the goal 400 for the month of june. Donations go towards purchasing a new android device that will be supported the next 4 years and new software and equipment for development. We can't have a finished project built with crusty equipment named after my grandfather...Remember to update your experience on Google Play for Sapphire.</text>
<date>3 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Spaces!">
<text>Join us on Spaces! Exclusive first looks, in-group discussion and more. HMU on hangouts for details.</text>
<date>19 May 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Ratings and Reviews">
<text>Don't forget to update your reviews on google play and xda labs! If you haven't had the moment to rate Sapphire UI, take the time todo so. Ratings are part of the community focus and user feedback program and updates usually are forged and based on feedback. Let us build something together.</text>
<date>12 May 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Backers">
<text>Grab an Onyx License to show off true backing support. Adds Onyx Subscriber to Sapphire launcher settings subtitle.</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Google Plus">
<text>Join the Google Plus Group to get in on exclusive sneak peaks, dev previews, and one on one dev support!</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Papers">
<text>Wallpapers will be updated on a monthly basis based on top picks of the android communities.</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome and Thankyou for your support!">
<text>Enjoy your stay, Ask questions, get involved with the communities and stay active! Sapphire UI is the community custom launcher powered by google exclusively for Android 5.0+</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

</news>
