<news>

<newsitem headline="Reminder">
<text>Please take the time to read the latest blog on GSD. It has todo with you and the futurw i hold for you. </text>
<date>7 August 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Onyx Key price drop">
<text>Prices are now 6.35 for an Onyx License. Thank you for using Sapphire Launcher! Your exclusive reward will come in due time... </text>
<date>2 August 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Dev Preview 11.3.1">
<text>Dev Preview build 11.3.1 is now available on xda labs. For more information, check the google plus Group feed</text>
<date>21 July 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Papers Maintenance Issues">
<text>Their are reports of the Sapphire wallpaper archives not loading correctly or crashing on loading all wallpapers. This issue is being tracked.</text>
<date>26 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Update 11.3 schedule update">
<text>Notice! 11.3 official update will be released on Google Play after the dev preview program has ended that is now available on xda labs. The dev preview program is to crank out any flaws or bugs regarding the revamped updated expected to drop in August. Regards</text>
<date>26 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Ratings and Reviews">
<text>Don't forget to update your reviews on google play and xda labs! If you haven't had the moment to rate Sapphire UI, take the time todo so. Ratings are part of the community focus and user feedback program and updates usually are forged and based on feedback. Let us build something together.</text>
<date>12 May 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Backers">
<text>Grab an Onyx License to show off true backing support. Adds Onyx Subscriber to Sapphire launcher settings subtitle.</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Google Plus">
<text>Join the Google Plus Group to get in on exclusive sneak peaks, dev previews, and one on one dev support!</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="OTA Sapphire Wallpapers">
<text>Wallpapers will be updated on a priority/request basis based on community needs and wants.</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome and Thankyou for your support!">
<text>Enjoy your stay, Ask questions, get involved with the communities and stay active! Sapphire UI is the community custom launcher powered by google exclusively for Android 5.0+</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

</news>
