<news>
  
<newsitem headline="Record Breaking Revenue">
<text>You guys have broken the record of Premium license purchased for the month. This is excellent news! Keep it up! This revenue will be invested in upgraded equipment for my Android Workstation which desperately needs it for the new projects coming. Without these upgrades, these projects won't be possible. THANKYOU!</text>
<date>5 December 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Thankyou">
<text>This phrase says it all. The two years that some of you have fully been dedicated means so much to me as a developer. You will soon see the light of a sequal in the new year. A revised and more powerful launcher is in the works for Android 6.0+. Sapphire Launcher EX is coming in 2017.</text>
<date>5 December 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Wallpaper Patch">
<text>Wallpapers should soon be working correctly in the cloud. A patch is currently being worked on from my end.</text>
<date>5 December 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Update 12.1">
<text>The end of the year patch is currently in development. This update will fix a rotation bug reported by many, increase performance, higher resolution visuals for high end phones increased, visual changes to the launcher settings and a few extras. Updates will also feature less advancment after this update rolls out as well making this launcher nearing its Stable Branch. This is good and bad as updates will be less exciting and only provide security, performance and general patches. Good news is something special will be going in development soon. Stay tuned! Mid December this new update should be ready to roll out.</text>
<date>5 December 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Holiday Sale!">
<text>Premium and Onyx license are now on Sale through the month of December. This is your chance to lock yourself in to an array of premium projects I have to announce for 2017. Enjoy!</text>
<date>5 December 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Wanna Translate?">
<text>If you are a user interested in contributing to the project by translating Sapphire Launcher for your locale, please contact me on Hangouts or the Google Plus Group. Also take a look at the Sapphire Github. https://github.com/rgocal/SUI </text>
<date>30 October 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome and Thankyou for your support!">
<text>Enjoy your stay, Ask questions, get involved with the communities and stay active!</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

</news>
