<news>

<newsitem headline="Update and Review Ratings">
<text>Please take some time to update and review your rating on the latest version of Sapphire Launcher and any License you have purchased. Higher ratings get the launcher noticed, which increases user counts and revenue which increase the likely hood of bigger and better updates.</text>
<date>12 September 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Update 11.4. 00 Live">
<text>Download now on google play or xda labs. Caution, Tracking an issue with dark statusbar enabled that borks the widget container while adding widgets to your workspace. Disable tweak to retain momentum. Will be looking for a fix soon.</text>
<date>12 September 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Onyx and Premium License Update">
<text>A scheduled update is due in October for Onyx and Prem license for licensing validation. This action is being taken to verify users for future license cary-over. The license you own will be carried over to other applications to prevent double purchases.</text>
<date>8 September 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Onyx License Owners">
<text>An early access awaits you in the future.</text>
<date>8 September 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Google Plus">
<text>Join the Google Plus Group to get in on exclusive sneak peaks, dev previews, and one on one dev support!</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome and Thankyou for your support!">
<text>Enjoy your stay, Ask questions, get involved with the communities and stay active! Sapphire UI is the community custom launcher powered by google exclusively for Android 5.0+</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

</news>
