<news>

<newsitem headline="Soak Test">
<text>Once the new launcher settings is foeged, il be requesting users for soak testing 11.3. The opportunity will be shared to users in Sapphire UI's Spaces group. Il have more information as it becomes available.</text>
<date>26 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Papers Maintenance Issues">
<text>Their are reports of the Sapphire wallpaper archives not loading corrwctly or crqshing on loading all wallpapers. This issue is being tracked.</text>
<date>26 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Donations">
<text>Keys will be seeing a price drop on 11.3 release. This is to help raise money for the project and pay for my future project im raising money to fund. Gaining experience for a bigger project to learn more is our goal. June was actually the worse donation month so we will keep our heads high and continue slowly. The more donations, the higher value, the bigger and faster updates that are polished.</text>
<date>26 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Update 11.3 schedule update">
<text>A nasty dashclock bug has been discovered and is currently being tracked and worked on. This will delay the release of 11.3. I will be taking this opportunity to work on enhancing a few other features because of the delay. As of now, this update is being one of the most polished and big maintenance updates to expect this summer. Regards</text>
<date>26 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Game with the dev">
<text>HMU up on the Sony Playstation 4! PSN Dracos_Aura Favorite games are Battlefield and Destiny!</text>
<date>20 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="GocalSD Website Improvements">
<text>GSD has gone through some visual maintenance. Go ahead and check it out. More visual additions will be added soon as well as an exclusive section for Sapphire Launcher.</text>
<date>20 June 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Spaces!">
<text>Join us on Spaces! Exclusive first looks, in-group discussion and more. HMU on hangouts for details.</text>
<date>19 May 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Ratings and Reviews">
<text>Don't forget to update your reviews on google play and xda labs! If you haven't had the moment to rate Sapphire UI, take the time todo so. Ratings are part of the community focus and user feedback program and updates usually are forged and based on feedback. Let us build something together.</text>
<date>12 May 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Backers">
<text>Grab an Onyx License to show off true backing support. Adds Onyx Subscriber to Sapphire launcher settings subtitle.</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Google Plus">
<text>Join the Google Plus Group to get in on exclusive sneak peaks, dev previews, and one on one dev support!</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Papers">
<text>Wallpapers will be updated on a monthly basis based on top picks of the android communities.</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome and Thankyou for your support!">
<text>Enjoy your stay, Ask questions, get involved with the communities and stay active! Sapphire UI is the community custom launcher powered by google exclusively for Android 5.0+</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

</news>
