<news>
  
<newsitem headline="Premium License Code Redeemers">
<text>Congratulations to the winners who claimed Premium codes from the code brawl! See you guys next brawl! A perk of joining the Google Plus Sapphire Launcher Group.</text>
<date>26 August 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url> https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rgocal/Launcher3-1/master/launcher3/src/main/res/mipmap-hdpi/ic_launcher_home.png </image-url>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Project Niebieski">
<text>A new launcher experience will be revealed at the end of 2016 #Sapphyx #Bionx #Sapphire</text>
<date>26 August 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Update 11.4 Schedule">
<text>This update is scheduled to roll out near the end of the month or early September.</text>
<date>23 August 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Sapphire @GSD">
<text>The Sapphire Launcher page has gone live on GocalSD.Weebly.com head on over to check it out. Maybe one of your homescreen setups made an appearance! Share this page with friends, family and followers to help them get an idea of what Sapphire Launcher is and why it exist.</text>
<date>23 August 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Update 11.3.15">
<text>The new update is now available on Google Play and on XDA labs via the Stable branch. A big thankyou to dev previewers making this update possible and putting in an effort to possible request and general feedback on new and exciting tweaks, revamps and more.  More exciting things are in your future. Take the time to update your ratings on google play and post some general thoughts and feedback on Google Plus group!</text>
<date>14 August 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="User Feedback Program Survey">
<text>Their is a survey currently available on the Google Plus Community to voluntarily complete. Once complete, plus 1 the post and comment "done" and you will be entered in a Sapphire Launcher Premium license give away. This survery is to help fabricate a more professional future with the community and get some general feedback on our current use of Sapphire Launcher. </text>
<date>11 August 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Backers">
<text>Grab an Onyx License to show off true backing support. Adds Onyx Subscriber to Sapphire launcher settings subtitle. Also gains access to something special in the future.</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Google Plus">
<text>Join the Google Plus Group to get in on exclusive sneak peaks, dev previews, and one on one dev support!</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome and Thankyou for your support!">
<text>Enjoy your stay, Ask questions, get involved with the communities and stay active! Sapphire UI is the community custom launcher powered by google exclusively for Android 5.0+</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

</news>
