<news>

<newsitem headline="Wallpaper Archives Error">
<text>Users have reported that some categories of wallpapers are not loading properly and this issue is being tracked. Corrective action will be taken sometime this weekend. An update will not be required for this fix, stay tuned. </text>
<date>2 November 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Wanna Translate?">
<text>If you are a user interested in contributing to the project by translating Sapphire Launcher for your locale, please contact me on Hangouts or the Google Plus Group. Also take a look at the Sapphire Github. https://github.com/rgocal/SUI </text>
<date>30 October 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Progress Report!">
<text>Be sure to update your reviews of Sapphire Launcher on Google Play reflecting your experience with the 12.00 update. Also report back any flaws, spelling errors or hickups you have encountered so a patch can be built. Tablet support is also important.</text>
<date>30 October 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Update 12.00 Available!">
<text>You can grab the latest update for Sapphire Launcher now! https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.NxIndustries.Sapphire</text>
<date>30 October 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="New Wallpapers">
<text>Check the archives this weekend for new wallpapers collected from the community. Community members are welcomed to submit their own!</text>
<date>27 October 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Update and Review Ratings">
<text>Please take some time to update and review your rating on the latest version of Sapphire Launcher and any License you have purchased. Higher ratings get the launcher noticed, which increases user counts and revenue which increase the likely hood of bigger and better updates.</text>
<date>12 September 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Google Plus">
<text>Join the Google Plus Group to get in on exclusive sneak peaks, dev previews, and one on one dev support!</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome and Thankyou for your support!">
<text>Enjoy your stay, Ask questions, get involved with the communities and stay active! Sapphire UI is the community custom launcher powered by google exclusively for Android 5.0+</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

</news>
