<news>

<newsitem headline="Spaces!">
<text>Join us on Spaces! Exclusive first looks, in-group discussion and more. Details on google plus group.</text>
<date>19 May 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="Congratulations Winners!">
<text>Onyx Backers have been selected! For their privacy of data, the drawing was private as part of SUI's promise is security. I hope to see more of you in future drawings and promotions!</text>
<date>17 May 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Hotfix 11.2.1 Live">
<text>Make sure to accept this update on Google Play for security patches, performance patches and general fixes!</text>
<date>13 May 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Ratings and Reviews">
<text>Don't forget to update your reviews on google play and xda labs! If you haven't had the moment to rate Sapphire UI, take the time todo so. Ratings are part of the community focus and user feedback program and updates usually are forged and based on feedback. Let us build something together.</text>
<date>12 May 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Backers">
<text>Grab an Onyx License to show off true backing support. Adds Onyx Subscriber to Sapphire launcher settings subtitle.</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Update 11.2">
<text>Welcome to Sapphire UI Milestone 2! This update was forged on the innovation of the XDA and Google Plus Community Groups</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Google Plus">
<text>Join the Google Plus Group to get in on exclusive sneak peaks, dev previews, and one on one dev support!</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="SUI Papers">
<text>Wallpapers will be updated on a monthly basis based on top picks of the android communities.</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome and Thankyou for your support!">
<text>Enjoy your stay, Ask questions, get involved with the communities and stay active! Sapphire UI is the community custom launcher powered by google exclusively for Android 5.0+</text>
<date>22 April 2016</date>
<description/>
<technical-details/>
<image-url/>
</newsitem>

</news>
